IGOR PAPRZYCKI



PHONE

+48 504 781 817

EMAIL

igypap@gmail.com

GITHUB

github.com/igorpaprzycki

ADDRESS

Jana Kazimierza 11B/91 01-248 Warszawa POLAND

Summary

Ambitious, highly skilled professional with over one year of experience in software development. Possess strong software skills in JAVA technologies. Have analytical and problem-solving skills combined with passion and commitment to software engineering. In the past worked for four years in aviation industry as process automation engineer.

Technical skills

TECHNOLOGIES

- Java 8
- SpringBoot, Thymeleaf
- DB2, SQLite, MSSQL, SQLServer, Hibernate
- JUnit, EasyMock

DEV TOOLS

- Intellij IDEA
- SVN, GIT
- Maven, Gradle

CI TOOLS

- Jenkins
- Tomcat
- Atlassian Suite (JIRA, Confluence)
- Platforms: Linux, Windows

BASIC KNOWLEDGE

- HTML, CSS, Bootstrap
- Android (XML, ButterKnife, Activity Lifecycle)
- Android Studio

Experience

GOLDMAN SACHS JUNE 2017 - present

Analyst JAVA Developer

JAVA Developer in Investment Banking industry responsible for software development, deployment and testing, providing high quality code and on-time delivery. Working on Clearing House communication API implementation for internal clearing processes. Technology stack:

- JAVA 8, Spring, Maven, Gradle, JMS, SVN, Jenkins, Tomcat
- Test-driven development: JUnit, Groovy, EasyMock
- Databases: DB2
- Platforms: Linux (production), Windows (development)
- Project Management Tools: Atlassian Suite (JIRA, Confluence)

Freelancer APRIL 2016 - OCTOBER 2016

C++/QT Developer

The project deliverable was to develop GUI application providing MODBUS communication with industrial PLC controller & Ethernet IDS camera.

Application main tasks: calibration parameters settings, data acquisition, image capture, data analysis & report generation.

Technologies used: Qt Framework, MODBUS TCP/IP, multithreading, OpenCV library, STL containers.

.....

Institute of Aviation JANUARY 2013 - MAY 2017

ENGINEER

Aviation engines Fan Blade Out facility design and commissioning. The Warsaw Institute of Aviation center can now boast of having the world's largest vacuum chamber. Designed for Fan Blade detachment tests in largest turbine engines. It is 12 meters long, it has 5.5 meters in internal diameter and weighs 177 tons.

My responsibilities: Data Acquisition, sensor instrumentation & HMI systems design and commissioning. Works mainly with National Instruments hardware and LabVIEW software.

Courses

JAVA Bootcamp october 2016 - MARCH 2017

AkademiaKodu.pl

Java BootCamp programming course for Android and Spring web application development.

Education

Kielce University of Technology 2011 - 2012

MASTER OF SCIENCE (M. Sc.), Electrical Engineering

Graduation in 5% of the best University students.

Kielce University of Technology 2007 - 2011

FIRST DEGREE ENGINEER, Electrical Engineering